(Penny:)Why don't you come over next Saturday
and watch the game?
(Leonard:)Another football game?
(Penny:)They have them every week.
(Leonard:)Did not know that.
(Penny:)-You wanted to meet my friends.
-Sure.
(Penny:)Just--
I don't know much about football.
(Penny:)The guys' girlfriends
don't know football.
(Penny:)They just kind of drink
and talk in the kitchen.
(Leonard:)Great.
COMMENTATOR [ON TV]:
Looking left, he's got nothing.
-He drops off a screen, out of bounds--
-Okay, a completed pass.
(Leonard:)First down, New England.
(Leonard:)-I think I'm starting to get this.
-Really?
The only thing I've learned is that
American men love drinking beer...
(Raj:)...pee too often,
and have trouble getting erections.
(Leonard:)Focus on the game,
not the commercials, Raj.
If people cut back on the beer,
you could get out the bathroom...
(Raj:)...and satisfy your women
without pharmaceutical help.